# SAIA FONUA

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT



801-722-9592



Saiafonua@gmail.com



Lehi, UT 84043



Linkedin.com/in/saiafonua



Github.com/sfonua10

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Arts in Linguistics**

Brigham Young University 2012 - 2015

#### **Front-End Certification**

V School Bootcamp 2015 - 2016

#### **Online Education Platforms**

Udemy, FEM, FCC, and Member of The UtahJS Users Group 2016 – Present

#### SKILLS

Positive Teammate

**Strong Communication** 

Time and Task Management

Adaptability

**Quick Learning Ability** 

**Tech Proficient** 

**Problem Solving** 

High-End User Focused

#### PROFILE

Self-motivated Full Stack Developer with over 5+ years of experience. Passionate about quality work with teammates and helping software companies achieve long-term vision. Seeking opportunities to grow with a reputable company inside the Tech Industry.

#### STACK

- Reactjs
- Node.js
- Jest
- GIT
- SQL Server
- Express
- JavaScript
- Next.js
- GraphQL
- HTML5
- MongoDB
- Angular
- TypeScript
- Gatsby
- Rest (API's)
- CSS3-Flexbox/Grid
- Styled Components
- Jira

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER** (Contract)

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints | Riverton, UT | Sep 2021-Current

- Fix bugs and participate in code reviews and meetings
- Contribute to component library to enhance and fix components
- Build same pages from Angular code to Next.js & React

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Freelancer | Lehi, UT | Nov 2016 - Current (most recent projects listed)

- Built a Sales Leads Project with the MERN stack and Jest unit testing
- Quiz built with Gatsby, Styled Components, and Facebook SDK for Authentication
- Blog built with Reactjs, Gatsby, GraphQL, Styled Components and Sanity CMS
- Pooch/Poochfolio dog care app with team of three developers

### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Boostability/Manta | Remote | Oct 2020 - Feb 2021

- Create interactive web pages from UI wireframes
- Collaborate with product owners to design, test, and analyze tracking metrics
- Debug and implement features in app

# **SOFTWARE ENGINEER** (Contract)

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints | Riverton, UT | Feb 2019-Oct 2020

- · Performing bug fixes and code reviews to reduce technical debt
- Leaving source code readable, modular, performant, and accessible
- Created features, functionality, and capabilities with Reactjs & Nextjs